<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Mrityunjay Kumar</title>
    <link>https://mrityunjaykumar911.github.io/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Mrityunjay Kumar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mrityunjaykumar911.github.io/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Running Machine Learning as Service</title>
      <link>https://mrityunjaykumar911.github.io/publications/machinelearningasservice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrityunjaykumar911.github.io/publications/machinelearningasservice/</guid>
      <description>This talk looked at the nuances of deployment of Machine Learning models in production. In current era, when CI &amp;amp; CD are supported for almost all type of applications developed and with integration with services like GCP, AWS; one can deploy scalable solution at instant.
However, the idiosyncratic complexity for deployment of Machine learning model in robust system is still a mystry and many firms have invested for add-on frameworks for developing a comparable solution to push it to production environemnt, but many still face the challanges like scalability, latency etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning to fingerprint the latent structure in question articulation - ICMLA 2018</title>
      <link>https://mrityunjaykumar911.github.io/publications/icmla2018papertalentica/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrityunjaykumar911.github.io/publications/icmla2018papertalentica/</guid>
      <description>GOAL The goal of the project is to find techniques to generate application-specific fingerprints for data. There are many machine learning applications that need to incrementally evolve in their ability to process data. When data does not match the processing ability, we see unexpected results and system misbehavior. If we are able to generate fingerprints for classes of data, and if we can discard data that does not match known fingerprints, then we have better control over how unexpected data can influence underlying algorithms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fingerprinting Latent Structure in Data - DAIR IIT - Delhi</title>
      <link>https://mrityunjaykumar911.github.io/publications/dair-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrityunjaykumar911.github.io/publications/dair-presentation/</guid>
      <description>Title:
Fingerprinting Latent Structure in Data
Abstract:
As data-hungry algorithms find wide spread applications, there is an increased interest in exploring these algorithms in the context of small-data. In many niche industrial applications, data is not only held in secrecy for reasons of privacy and competitive advantage, but is also limited in volume and variety. Under these constraints, data-driven algorithms are expected to exhibit low application misbehavior. If one can discard data that does not match capabilities of underlying algorithms, there is better control over how unexpected data can influence the application behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>